{
  "questions": [
    {
      "options": [
        "High-level, often just-in-time compiled, and multi-paradigm programming language",
        "Dynamic typing, prototype-based object-orientation programming language",
        "A multi-paradigm language that supports event-driven, functional, and imperative programming styles",
        "All the above"
      ],
      "id": 1,
      "question": "<p>What is Javascript (Just google: wikipedia javascript and read first four paragraphs)</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "All the above"
    },
    {
      "options": ["boolean", "bulbuli", "number", "string"],
      "id": 2,
      "question": "<p>Which one is not a type of variable?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "bulbuli"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "parseFloat()",
        "parseString()",
        "parseNumber()",
        "parseInt()"
      ],
      "id": 3,
      "question": "<p>Which method is used to convert a string to an integer?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "parseInt()"
    },
    {
      "options": ["Netscape", "Google", "Facebook", "Firefox"],
      "id": 4,
      "question": "<p>Which company developed JavaScript? (feel free to google it)</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "Netscape"
    },
    {
      "options": ["/", "%", "*", "\\"],
      "id": 5,
      "question": "<p>Which one is not a mathematical operator in JS?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "\\"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "Set the value to 0",
        "Increase the value by 1",
        "Decrease the value by 1",
        "White plus toothpaste"
      ],
      "id": 6,
      "question": "<p>What does it mean by writing two plus signs after a number type variable?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "Increase the value by 1"
    },
    {
      "options": ["21", "8", "218", "29"],
      "id": 7,
      "question": "<p>If&nbsp;you have a var age = 21; and then you write age += 8; now what will be the value of the variable age?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "29"
    },
    {
      "options": ["mobile-price", "1bookName", "user9", "“temperature”"],
      "id": 8,
      "question": "<p>Which one is an acceptable variable name?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "user9"
    },
    {
      "options": ["7", "2", "5", "3"],
      "id": 9,
      "question": "<p>What will be the output of the code: console.log(17%5)</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "2"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "building  User Interface",
        "building Database",
        "building User Data Flow",
        "building  Shop"
      ],
      "id": 10,
      "question": "<p>React is mainly used&nbsp;for _______ (if needed, google it)</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "building  User Interface"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "class  = “myClass”",
        "Class = “myClass”",
        "className = “myClass”",
        "I don’t know"
      ],
      "id": 11,
      "question": "<p>How do you declare a class called “myClass” in react?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "className = “myClass”"
    },
    {
      "options": ["filter", "find", "map", "for"],
      "id": 12,
      "question": "<p>Which method will you use in react to display components for each object in an array?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "map"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "const { name, setName } =  useState(“JingaLala”);",
        "[name, setName] =  UseState(“JingaLala”);",
        "const ( name, setName ) =  useState(“JingaLala”);",
        "const [name, setName] =  useState(“JingaLala”);"
      ],
      "id": 13,
      "question": "<p>How will create a state with a default value “JingaLala”?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "const [name, setName] =  useState(“JingaLala”);"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "We  should use class instead of className",
        "class is a reserved keyword in javascript",
        "We can use any name "
      ],
      "id": 14,
      "question": "<p>Why can’t we declare a class with the “class” keyword in React?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "class is a reserved keyword in javascript"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "Javascript Html ",
        "Javascript XML",
        "React XML",
        "Javascript Http"
      ],
      "id": 15,
      "question": "<p>What is&nbsp;&nbsp;JSX?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "Javascript XML"
    },
    {
      "options": ["Uppercase", "Lowercase", "I can use Both"],
      "id": 16,
      "question": "<p>When creating a component in React, the first letter of that function name should be in ____</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "Uppercase"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "function  nayika() { return <h3>Mousumi </h3>}",
        "function  Nokiya()  [ return <h3> Mousumi <h3> ]",
        "function  Nayika() ( return <h3> Mousumi </h3> )",
        "function  Nayika() { return <h3> Mousumi </h3>   }"
      ],
      "id": 17,
      "question": "<p>What is the correct way of creating a component in react?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "function  Nayika() { return <h3> Mousumi </h3>   }"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "Chicken Salad Sandwich",
        "Cascading Style Sheet",
        "Central Security Service",
        "Cold Shrimp Salad"
      ],
      "id": 18,
      "question": "<p>What is the meaning of CSS?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "Cascading Style Sheet"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "<css></css>",
        "<color></color>",
        "<style></style>",
        "<head></head>"
      ],
      "id": 19,
      "question": "<p>Which tag will you use to add style on your website?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "<style></style>"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "p{ blue: color }",
        "p{ color = blue }",
        "p{ color : blue; }",
        "p{ text: “blue”; }"
      ],
      "id": 20,
      "question": "<p>How will you add blue color to all paragraph tags?</p><p>Hint: write four parts of a style rule</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "p{ color : blue; }"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "color:purple;",
        "background color:purple;",
        "background-color:purple;",
        "backgroundColor:purple;"
      ],
      "id": 21,
      "question": "<p><span style=\"background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);\">How would you set a purple background color to an element?</span></p>",
      "correctAnswer": "background-color:purple;"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "p{ width: 1/2 }",
        "p{ width: 50%; }",
        "p{ width: 0.5; }",
        "p{ width: half; }"
      ],
      "id": 22,
      "question": "<p>How to set the width of all paragraph tags as half of the available width? </p><p>Hint: think about the total width as a percent and then think about the half of the width</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "p{ width: 50%; }"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "The value of multiple ID attributes has to be unique",
        "Use ID to style a specific HTML element",
        "Same ID should be used in different HTML tags"
      ],
      "id": 23,
      "question": "<p>Which one is not true?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "Same ID should be used in different HTML tags"
    },
    {
      "options": [
        "Separate class names by a whitespace",
        "Separate class names by a comma",
        "You cannot apply more than one class name",
        "Use id"
      ],
      "id": 24,
      "question": "<p>How can we add multiple classes to an HTML element?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "Separate class names by a whitespace"
    },
    {
      "options": ["One", "Two", "Seven", "Four"],
      "id": 25,
      "question": "<p>How many values a margin style rule cannot have?</p>",
      "correctAnswer": "Seven"
    }
  ]
}
